[
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "There might not be enough guides for this weekend’s art exhibit.",
    "answer": "provide audio guide devices / increase the size of tour groups / make a pamphlet, and give it to visitors. / prepare some drinks, and let them enjoy their time at the art exhibit."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Some gym members aren’t returning their used towels.",
    "answer": "post a notice at the exit / will remind them to return the towels / get a deposit, and deduct money if they don’t return the towels."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Library visitors can’t use the main entrance during construction.",
    "answer": "set up a sign in front of the building / can direct people to the side door / post a notice online, and suggest a detour to the back door."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "We’re hosting an event tomorrow, but our banquet hall doesn’t have enough tables.",
    "answer": "rent some portable tables immediately / ask staff to set them up tomorrow morning / buy some tables today. Because we are always having problem with a shortage of tables."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "The event schedule needs to be changed due to the weather, and participants must be informed.",
    "answer": "send text messages to attendees / have the phone numbers of the participants / post a notice online. Some people will come and check it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "The hotel’s ocean-view rooms are popular, but the standard ones aren’t.",
    "answer": "offer discounts on standard rooms / update furniture in the rooms"
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "the conference room cannot hold everyone.",
    "answer": "rent another venue / use a large hall at a nearby university"
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "insufficient computers.",
    "answer": "borrow some computers from public institutions nearby / They always have extra computers. Actually, something like this happened before. That time, we borrowed several laptops from the public library."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "the supplier because they will increase the price.",
    "answer": "look for a new supplier / There are so many suppliers in the city. / Post a notice online, and get some proposals from many different suppliers."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "imporve a gallery service",
    "answer": "offer a free painting class for visitors / They can make good memories with families and friends. / prepare some comfortable sofas and tables / More people will come and relax."
  }
]